Hi,

I graduated from the Wrocław University of Technology, where I wrote genetic algorithms, generated fractals and wrote my own ray tracing image generating engine in C ++. After graduation, I programmed in java, action script, php, ruby and c #. I got to know GIT and SVN very well. I worked in Wrocław and for two years in Toronto, Canada, using AR (mobile) technologies, data streaming using the Unity engine.

At game jams, I successfully created playable prototypes, winning TK game jam 2016 or taking high places in others.

Thanks to my trip to Canada, I know English fluently. Thanks to prototyping on game jams, I am able to create a prototype of a new system very quickly. Thanks to the studies with this specific development path, I know c ++, genetic algorithms, advanced artificial intelligence.

In 2021 and 2022, as part of my work at Dali Games, I created Dali Engine: a game development tool (in c #) in which two adventure games were already created.

In 2022:
- I wrote a tetris game in c++ using SFML (link here: https://github.com/kbobnis/tetris),
- I learned the basics of math from the book: Fletcher Dunn - 3D Math Primer for Graphics and Game Development, the chapter with: Coordinate Systems, Vectors, Multiple Coordinate Systems, Matrices, Transformations.

I believe that I will be a great addition to your team.


Krzysiek Bobnis